1776, when we founded the light to all nations,
and it's something really that is an amazing thing
came out of that date.
It's called the United States of America.
In honor of this momentous anniversary,
I hope that all countries who find inspiration in our example
will join us in renewing our commitment, values,
and those values, really, that we hold so dear together.
Let us defend free speech and free expression.
Let us protect religious liberty,
including for the most persecuted religion on the planet today.
It's called Christianity.
And let us safeguard our sovereignty and cherish qualities
that have made each of our nations so special,
incredible, and extraordinary.
In closing, I just want to repeat that immigration
and the high cost of so-called green renewable energy
is destroying a large part of the free world
and a large part of our planet.
Countries that cherish